[Music]
I see the Panic somewhere in your eyes
yeah in your
eyes I want it's brought us here
tonight you're back to life if you're
going to leave me hang then you're going
to leave me dead I'm never going home if
you're not there I want to give into
your dark
Temptation I want to touch you like
nobody does oh people like you and me
were B around so where we go when my Dan
is done I want to give to you dark
Temptation I want to touch you like
nobody does oh people like you and me
were Bor to run so where we go when the
dance is
done I want to taste the secrets that
you hide and make a
mind come take me to the edge of
afterlife
and take your time if you're going to
leave me hang then you're going to leave
me Dan oh I'm never going home if you're
not there I want to give into your dark
Temptation I want to touch you like
nobody does oh people like you and me
will B around so when we go when the
dancing done I want to give to you D
Temptation I want to touch you like
nobody does w people like you and me
we're B to run so where we go when the
dances done
[Applause]
when the D and star